What if a pill could make you rich and powerful?
Limitless is a thriller, mystery, science fiction film directed by Neil Burger.
The life of an unsuccessful writer is transformed by a top-secret 'smart drug' that
allows him to use 100% of his brain and become a perfect version of himself.
His enhanced abilities soon attract shadowy forces that threaten his new life.
Edward Morra, played by Bradley Cooper.
Carl Van Loon, played by Robert De Niro.
Lindy, played by Abbie Cornish.
Gennady, played by Andrew Howard.
Melissa, played by Anna Friel.
Vernon, played by Johnny Whitworth.
Limitless is a 2011 American science fiction thriller film
directed by Neil Burger and written by Leslie Dixon.
Loosely based on the 2001 novel The Dark Fields by Alan Glynn, the film stars Bradley
Cooper, Abbie Cornish, Robert De Niro, Andrew Howard and Anna Friel.
It follows Edward Morra, a struggling writer who is introduced to a drug called NZT-48 that
greatly enhances his brain function, which helps him improve his lifestyle.
Limitless was released on March 18, 2011.
Critical reviews were mixed-to-positive, and the film became a box-office
success, grossing more than $161 million on a budget of $27 million.
A television series covering events that take place after the film debuted
on September 22, 2015, but was canceled after one season.
The film explores themes of new york city, medicine, politician, iq, pill.
The tone is mind_bending and thought_provoking and intense.